Mugi, are you ready?
Wait, hold on a sec.
I'm the assistant today.
Are you stupid or something, Mugi?
I'll take care of that for you.
Now go on, get out of here.
You two go get some crepes together.
Sanai.
You heading home now, Hanabi?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Would you mind walking home together?
We haven't really been able to hang out that much with each other this year.
Thanks for waiting.
Yeah, well, um...
Oh, that's right.
You've been walking home with Mugi lately.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
He is your boyfriend, after all.
He comes first.
Next time, okay?
Man, he's so lucky.
Well, he is pretty popular with the ladies.
You know, they make a good couple.
Are you sure you didn't want to walk with your friend?
I'm good.
Give me some of that.
You stop that right now!
You scared me.
What?
Who exactly are you?
You?
You're right.
Mugi and I are childhood friends from the same apartment building.
Aw, aren't you cute?
Did you know that you and Mugi look like the perfect image of a prince and princess when you're together?
A prince and princess? How romantic.
As a young girl, the thought of that captured my imagination.
I'm a princess.
I spent a whole year growing out my hair.
I stopped playing with all the smelly boys.
And I spent my time collecting only cute things.
I tried my hardest to become a princess worthy of a real prince.
So then, all that was left was for a prince to notice me.
And then my dream would come true.
Yeah, so, um...
This is Noriko Kamomebata.
Mocha!
She's my childhood friend.
This is Hanabi Yasuraoka, my girlfriend.
I'm not lying.
That can't be!
Uh, I remember you from grade school.
Huh? You know her?
Let me see...
Kamomekamokamo, that's it?
That's too many Kamos!
Then, Noriko.
Of course that's what you would remember!
It's Mocha Kamomebata!
For the record, Mocha is short for meeting the most cutest angel, Mocha!
I won't answer to anything else!
Yeah, yeah.
As I recall, you've always been a pain in the butt, now haven't you?
And as I remember correctly, you were always an awful, ungrateful person!
Why is someone like you dating Moogie anyway?
Poor Moogie getting tricked by a girl like this!
You just pretend to be nice in front of him, don't you?
Not at all.
Wow, I'm impressed you noticed.
You're right.
She can be horrible.
Sometimes.
You're one to talk, Moogie.
What are you saying?
Is that what you like?
Well, it's just a part that makes her Hanabi after all.
Thanks.
I like everything about you too, Moogie.
Listen up, kid.
I wouldn't go around clinging on to things...
...that aren't yours.
So, you know...
Yesterday...
Did you have to be so harsh to her?
What do you mean by that?
She likes you, doesn't she?
Yeah?
So what?
Well, that's just it.
Actually, why don't you turn her down properly?
I didn't notice you looking at her in that lustful way that you have.
It's the nice thing to do, after all.
Well...
Look, I understand a part of you cares about her.
Ow!
Come on.
You're just clinging to your superiority.
Why does it bother you?
Hm?
Is it because you want me all to yourself?
You're jealous?
Don't be such an idiot.
Look, I'm just possessive.
That's all.
I don't know.
Is that really it?
Who knows?
I have to fight for my life every day on this thing.
There's something wrong with Japan's commuter rush.
I want to see Mugi and his handsome face.
I hate wasting my time always thinking about him.
It's unbecoming of a princess.
Plus, it hurts so much thinking about him like that.
I just end up recreating him in my mind to fit my needs.
Scary.
Oh.
You getting some bread too?
Um, yeah.
Here.
A sweet and savory one.
He got the ones I wanted without asking.
Mugi!
I love you!
I can't breathe!
Let go of me, Mocha!
Oh, Mugi!
The time I get to be with him is the best!
That's exactly what I live for.
Huh?
I'm so jealous of your lunch.
I've got fried chicken.
You want some?
Yeah.
Say, ah!
Ah!
The fried chicken disappeared.
Oh, I think you're right.
You think it's poltergeists?
Hey!
Don't ignore me!
Cut it out, it hurts!
You're the little brat that needs to cut it out.
What the hell are you doing tagging along during our lunch date
and being so damn annoying?
Didn't I warn you before about this?
You... just shut out!
Is she an animal?
Evil succubus!
I bet you don't even like Mugi that much anyway!
She's just using you, Mugi!
She wants to brag that she's with you because you're so cool and popular in school!
I know that's all she cares about!
Yeah, whatever.
I see. You're very observant.
Stop acting like this is all okay with you, Mugi!
Fine, but mark my words!
I'm never giving up!
Excuse me!
Oh, she ran away.
Don't run away if you're not gonna give up.
Well, she's just frightened of you.
She was even polite.
She's so irritating!
Just the worst!
Using?
Hey! Stop!
Don't run in the hallway!
Okay!
I've always wanted to say that.
Just like on TV when the kids are running in the hall.
Good for you.
Anyway, why is it that I have to help you with this again?
Uh...
Because it's hard to ask anybody besides you.
What am I ever going to do with you?
So, where are we taking these papers?
Over to the language prep room.
Uh...
Doesn't that mean...
We're all alone!
This is it.
I can't ruin it and be nervous.
Leave the handouts there.
What I need to do here is...
That was heavy.
I need Brother to look at me.
I need to make him see me as a woman.
Even just a little.
Uh...
A piano?
That must be her.
Isn't she great?
I can always hear it.
Obviously a stupid music teacher is going to know how to play the piano!
Don't say that into the mic!
Get into the mic!
You ever consider giving up?
You've got two.
Listen, Hanabi.
There's plenty of other hot guys around here.
Uh...
Don't worry.
I don't mean me or anything like that.
You have to sing too!
What?
Brother's very...
Brother is here...
Brother is cool, you got that?!
Oh, you got that?
Don't cry.
You get it, don't you?
You're in the same situation.
You know that it's not a matter of deciding to just give them up or not.
Once you've fallen, you can't think of anyone else but them.
I know.
I get it.
Why did I end up having to fall for them?
But it doesn't always feel painful.
That's why I can't bring myself to wish that we'd never met.
That would...
How do I say?
Make it even worse to bear.
I'm sorry.
What?
What now?
Stick out your tongue.
Mugi.
Mugi?
Mugi, touch me.
Wait, hey, Mugi.
Don't you mean... brother?
You're right.
Mugi...
Don't you mean... brother?
You're right.
Mugi...
I didn't think I'd think of that with you.
What's more, that I'd be relieved.
I think...
I'd rather she yelled at me.
Evil Succubus!
I bet you don't even like Mugi that much anyway!
She's just using you, Mugi!
Using?
What if... the one being used...
is actually her?
Ah! Sanai! Good morning!
Hey! What's wrong, Hanabi?
Your face is bright red!
I slept in late.
Turns out I had plenty of time, huh?
Looks like it.
You... want to talk about romance?
Huh? Seems harmless to me. You should go do it.
Hmm... what am I supposed to talk about?
Poor thing. You don't have a lot of female friends.
I do too.
Yeah?
I'm being serious!
Like who, then?
Like... Sanai. So there.
Is that it?
Hanabi! That's why you should go meet with them.
Fine, then.
Is he... going to kiss me?
Good luck, then.
What is this? Why did...
Weirdo. It's a little...
like he's my boyfriend.
So we thought it would be wise to talk to you
about fixing her boy problems.
Huh?
So Ayumi here has grown up with a childhood friend named Hiro.
Growing up close by,
they just naturally started going out together
by the time they reached junior high.
And being so young and naive,
they innocently promised to be together forever, but...
But?
They ended up in different high schools
and Hiro cheated on her.
Oh.
But Ayumi isn't able to give him up
and told him she'll be the other woman if need be.
Huh?
But Ayumi senior at school saw the whole ugly thing.
Who?
And now Ayumi has been gradually moved
by the senior's kindness.
But she can't bring herself to end things with Hiro just yet.
So now she's with both Hiro and the senior at her school.
What?
Just wait a minute here.
So you're basically just doing the same thing as Hiro did to you?
Well, I guess that's true.
As her closest friend, I want her to be with the senior.
Don't you agree, Hanabi?
Uh...
This is heavy. Why me?
Well, who do you like the most between them, Ayumi?
That's the problem. I can't decide.
Huh?
She can't choose.
I don't understand that.
If I could have things work out with Brother, I'd do it in a heartbeat.
Mugi would too.
Hmm.
I guess I can't really empathize with this girl's problems.
If that's it, then just choose the senior already.
He's got good qualities his parents would like.
Huh? You really believe it's him?
If you really like both of these guys you're dealing with...
Huh?
As much as it hurts, it's a lot better to feel the pain.
Um...
It's not that I like them so much it actually hurts.
It's that it's painful trying to choose which one is the best.
I don't want to make the wrong choice and regret it.
Yeah, that's it exactly!
Who wants to regret their decision?
In that case, don't you think the senior is best?
I don't know. I really like looking at Hiro's face.
But you'll have a better future with your senior.
Hiro only has sports going for him after all.
What would you do, Hanabi?
What... are they serious?
Hey, Sanai.
Hm? What's up?
I was just wondering...
Do you like anyone?
What?
Where's this coming from?
So, yes then.
Please tell me, Sanai.
You didn't fall for them because of their specifications or something superficial like that, right?
Huh?
Well, I mean, their abilities are a part of them, I guess. But... I didn't fall for them because they're talented. It's not like I went and thinking I'd get something out of it or anything, right?
Oh, Sanai!
Huh? That's why I love you so much!
I feel exactly the same way.
That's not how you should base love.
It shouldn't be how you do that at all.
That's right. You have a boyfriend now.
Hey, Sanai.
Yeah?
Do you want to come spend the night tomorrow?
Hm?
What?!
Again?
Why?
So dumb!
Why am I getting ready for a sleepover?!
So, it seems like you have a big time crush too, Sanai.
How does an all night girl party sound? We can talk all night long.
Oh crap! Are we going to sleep in the same bed together? What will I do?!
Let me get this straight. Can you basically only get along with Sanai?
You can be such a tool. Besides, all I need is Sanai.
Oh.
I wonder what it's called when it's between girls.
A girl party?
Coming!
I'm glad you came.
Come on inside.
Hey.
Thank you for inviting me.
It's cause we're girls.
That's why it's not such a big deal.
I get to be closer than others.
I should consider myself lucky.
Yeah.
Just stay positive.
Well.
That's what I thought anyway.
I really thought that's all it would be.
So why?
Why did I...
I screwed it all up.
I'm an idiot.
I just...
wanna die.
I'm an idiot.
I just...
wanna die.